CALDER MARSHALL Web Developer

SUMMARY

Hello, my name is Calder. I am a software engineer interested in the pursuit of knowledge and commitment to self-Improvement. My leadership experience and time spent on the make line create comfortability in team & individual dynamics. My greatest weakness might be taking on too many projects at once, either for business or pleasure. I always finish my projects, but my attention to detail can sometimes be self-deprecating. Contact me and ask about my latest venture!

CONTACT

404-907-9812
Atlanta, GA
cmarshall72@gmail.com
caldermarshall.com
https://github.com/CalderMarshall
https://www.linkedin.com/in/calder-marshall69a064138/

SKILLS

JavaScript, Node, Express, SQL, HTML, CSS, Python, jQuery, Bootstrap, zsh

PERSONAL

Leadership: Eagle Scout, Troop 554 Volunteering: Open Hand Atlanta

EDUCATION

DigitalCrafts

16 Week immersive coding bootcamp Feb-May 2017 Cohort

Mercer University

2013-2016 Stetson School of Business Bachelor of Business Administration

Auburn University

2010 - 2013 Harbert College of Business 92 semester hours

PROJECTS

GetFresh

Full Stack Farmer's Market Web App https://github.com/dc-feb-2017cohort/freshToDeath

Blackjack

jQuery Card Game https://github.com/CalderMarshall/blac kjack

EXPERIENCE

Mellow Mushroom

Line Cook

Atlanta 2015-2017, Auburn 2013-2014 Worked all lines, ensuring quality of dishes and timeliness in a ~100 seat restaurant.

Sweetwater Pools 2011

Lifeguard Manager Atlanta Summers 2010 & 2011 Managed team of lifeguards on shift, ensured safety of guests, adjusted water chemistry.